https://searchdogfoundation.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - National Disaster Search Dog Foundation
AboutHome PageOur MissionOur FounderOur BoardOur StaffFAQsVideosSocializeContactProgramCanine RecruitmentCanine Training ProgramHow Search Teams DeployLifetime Care ProgramOur Search TeamsRetired DogsRainbow BridgeNewsDeploymentsNTCNational Training CenterNTC Site MapNTC Tour Interest FormWorkshopsNational Training Center (NTC) Training Request FormGiveJoin the Bark ForceLeave a LegacySponsor a Search DogCorporate PartnersIRA RolloverWorkplace GivingVolunteerDonateShop SDFDonate a Dog
National Disaster Search Dog Foundation Strengthening disaster response in America
Skip to content AboutHome PageOur MissionOur FounderOur BoardOur StaffFAQsVideosSocializeContactProgramCanine RecruitmentCanine Training ProgramHow Search Teams DeployLifetime Care ProgramOur Search TeamsRetired DogsRainbow BridgeNewsDeploymentsNTCNational Training CenterNTC Site MapNTC Tour Interest FormWorkshopsNational Training Center (NTC) Training Request FormGiveJoin the Bark ForceLeave a LegacySponsor a Search DogCorporate PartnersIRA RolloverWorkplace GivingVolunteerDonateShop SDFDonate a Dog
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicySafeguarding your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online and off-line information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. The Search Dog Foundation is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.The information we collectThis notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Search Dog Foundation website and in written or spoken communication. The types of personal information collected are:NameAddress (for shipping, billing and sending gifts)Email addressPhone numberCredit Card InformationOn some pages of our web site and in some off-line communications regarding dedications, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s mailing address. Or, if you want to make a donation in honor of someone and have that person receive notice of that donation, you will need to submit the honoree’s mailing address or email address.The way we use informationWe use the information you provide about yourself when making a donation or placing an order only to complete that transaction. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that transaction. If we have trouble processing a transaction, this contact information is used to get in touch with you, our supporter.We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order or dedicating a donation only to ship the product or provide notice of the donation. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill customers for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that transaction.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not shared with any outside parties.Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online or off-line in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our commitment to data securityThis website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, the information is protected both online and off-line. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.We provide Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protection or SSL technology to protect the web site and our users in three essential ways:An SSL Certificate enables encryption of sensitive information during online transactions.Each SSL Certificate contains unique, authenticated information about the certificate owner.A Certificate Authority verifies the identity of the certificate owner when it is issued.Our commitment to children’s privacyProtecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information from our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.How to contact usShould you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email Serenity Nichols at serenity@searchdogfoundation.org.
IMPORTANT NOTICE In accordance with federal guidelines related to the novel coronavirus (COVID-19) pandemic, all Search Dog Foundation staff who are non-essential to our canine care and campus operations will be working remotely.
Rest assured that our canines in training who live on campus are being well cared for by our Canine Care team and are continuing to get their daily exercise in. A core group of our dedicated Canine Care staff are staying on campus and are taking the dogs on daily hikes, completing core strength workout sessions in our canine gym, and having plenty of free play time in the yards. These team members are taking every precaution with regard to extra sanitization measures and physically distancing themselves from each other during this time while still ensuring our canines get the mental and physical stimulation, love and care they deserve.
We are so grateful to all the first responders, health care and other industry workers who are on the front lines, helping to care for others. Please take care of each other – we thank you all for your support during this time, we so appreciate all of you being Part of the Search!
Follow Us FacebookInstagramTwitterLatest NewsCorporate Partners (1)Deployment Reports (104)Major Deployments (7)Field Report (1)Lifetime Care (1)Newsletters (16)Press Articles (60)Rainbow Bridge (81)SDF Features (125)Think this is paw-some?Share this article!
National Training Center
6800 Wheeler Canyon Rd. Santa Paula, CA 93060 Phone: 888-4K9-HERO Tax ID #77-0412509
PRIVACY POLICY|990 FORM & AUDITED FINANCIALS|Careers|
Search for:
Search Back to Top
FacebookInstagramTwitter© 2020 National Disaster Search Dog Foundation. All Rights Reserved
